const questions = [

    {
        question: "10 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['45', '30', '20', '82'],
        answer: "20"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['20', '6', '26', '69'],
        answer: "6"
    },
    
     {
        question: "2 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['27', '86', '80', '10'],
        answer: "10"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['97', '47', '22', '62'],
        answer: "22"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['66', '30', '73', '46'],
        answer: "66"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['43', '6', '26', '86'],
        answer: "6"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['77', '57', '60', '27'],
        answer: "60"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['97', '21', '93', '11'],
        answer: "21"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['120', '31', '23', '17'],
        answer: "120"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['96', '62', '92', '79'],
        answer: "96"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['61', '8', '43', '79'],
        answer: "8"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['89', '15', '15', '26'],
        answer: "15"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['48', '78', '53', '36'],
        answer: "36"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['22', '87', '52', '77'],
        answer: "77"
    },
    
     {
        question: "2 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['13', '12', '89', '72'],
        answer: "12"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['32', '25', '64', '33'],
        answer: "32"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['42', '55', '18', '77'],
        answer: "77"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['54', '21', '64', '55'],
        answer: "55"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['80', '54', '14', '53'],
        answer: "80"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['71', '61', '40', '54'],
        answer: "54"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['64', '90', '72', '10'],
        answer: "90"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['40', '24', '59', '22'],
        answer: "22"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['66', '98', '14', '40'],
        answer: "14"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['71', '12', '74', '28'],
        answer: "12"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['28', '67', '1', '40'],
        answer: "40"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['35', '38', '67', '33'],
        answer: "35"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['74', '65', '99', '4'],
        answer: "4"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['10', '64', '97', '108'],
        answer: "108"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['8', '78', '35', '5'],
        answer: "8"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['80', '97', '51', '110'],
        answer: "110"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['70', '72', '33', '1'],
        answer: "33"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['99', '99', '7', '9'],
        answer: "99"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['26', '7', '28', '35'],
        answer: "35"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['28', '35', '79', '1'],
        answer: "35"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['36', '16', '34', '16'],
        answer: "16"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['26', '79', '33', '67'],
        answer: "33"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['24', '2', '94', '73'],
        answer: "24"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['29', '38', '14', '56'],
        answer: "56"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['44', '8', '89', '30'],
        answer: "8"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['10', '55', '34', '70'],
        answer: "10"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['37', '17', '36', '98'],
        answer: "36"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['51', '90', '14', '54'],
        answer: "54"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['90', '96', '2', '95'],
        answer: "96"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['4', '61', '47', '32'],
        answer: "4"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['100', '77', '87', '72'],
        answer: "72"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['11', '10', '5', '61'],
        answer: "10"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['58', '72', '39', '110'],
        answer: "110"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['24', '29', '67', '5'],
        answer: "24"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['7', '81', '14', '8'],
        answer: "7"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['81', '36', '69', '64'],
        answer: "81"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['44', '58', '61', '42'],
        answer: "44"
    },
    
     {
        question: "2 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['34', '99', '68', '16'],
        answer: "16"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['17', '79', '3', '36'],
        answer: "36"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['68', '90', '72', '91'],
        answer: "90"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['79', '91', '99', '54'],
        answer: "54"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['12', '70', '70', '12'],
        answer: "12"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['89', '7', '64', '22'],
        answer: "7"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['57', '46', '120', '33'],
        answer: "120"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['12', '28', '62', '48'],
        answer: "12"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['97', '60', '55', '93'],
        answer: "55"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['74', '65', '14', '33'],
        answer: "33"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['90', '8', '78', '83'],
        answer: "90"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['92', '33', '33', '95'],
        answer: "33"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['86', '12', '28', '33'],
        answer: "33"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['40', '24', '32', '90'],
        answer: "24"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['46', '25', '30', '92'],
        answer: "30"
    },
    
     {
        question: "2 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['37', '59', '21', '12'],
        answer: "12"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['15', '66', '26', '60'],
        answer: "15"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['80', '47', '12', '82'],
        answer: "12"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['52', '29', '45', '49'],
        answer: "45"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['48', '54', '37', '90'],
        answer: "48"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['55', '85', '83', '66'],
        answer: "66"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['90', '73', '82', '75'],
        answer: "90"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['10', '21', '64', '12'],
        answer: "12"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['65', '50', '11', '41'],
        answer: "50"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['66', '81', '67', '70'],
        answer: "66"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['36', '1', '46', '86'],
        answer: "36"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['85', '30', '42', '64'],
        answer: "42"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['28', '73', '74', '48'],
        answer: "48"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['87', '144', '45', '24'],
        answer: "144"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['48', '32', '94', '40'],
        answer: "40"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['24', '85', '47', '16'],
        answer: "24"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['8', '19', '73', '26'],
        answer: "8"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['6', '72', '100', '76'],
        answer: "72"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['23', '70', '30', '62'],
        answer: "30"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['4', '100', '75', '12'],
        answer: "12"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['24', '49', '38', '11'],
        answer: "11"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['48', '18', '69', '69'],
        answer: "18"
    },
    
     {
        question: "2 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['36', '24', '54', '87'],
        answer: "24"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['93', '38', '66', '18'],
        answer: "18"
    },
    
     {
        question: "2 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['69', '16', '6', '86'],
        answer: "6"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['68', '48', '39', '72'],
        answer: "72"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['31', '27', '36', '1'],
        answer: "27"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['56', '7', '48', '62'],
        answer: "7"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['54', '21', '16', '85'],
        answer: "21"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['13', '5', '67', '36'],
        answer: "5"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['66', '87', '9', '9'],
        answer: "9"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['47', '68', '19', '10'],
        answer: "10"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['65', '31', '14', '72'],
        answer: "72"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['91', '58', '30', '96'],
        answer: "30"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['53', '11', '4', '32'],
        answer: "32"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['30', '42', '75', '36'],
        answer: "30"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['26', '15', '6', '110'],
        answer: "110"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['6', '64', '36', '15'],
        answer: "64"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['44', '76', '17', '16'],
        answer: "16"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['8', '79', '20', '90'],
        answer: "8"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['88', '93', '50', '6'],
        answer: "6"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['52', '71', '100', '28'],
        answer: "100"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['11', '78', '20', '110'],
        answer: "110"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['88', '4', '40', '48'],
        answer: "4"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['41', '68', '36', '36'],
        answer: "36"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['53', '9', '40', '79'],
        answer: "9"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['88', '4', '25', '58'],
        answer: "88"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['69', '61', '80', '90'],
        answer: "80"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['27', '32', '21', '86'],
        answer: "21"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['47', '26', '2', '4'],
        answer: "2"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['40', '22', '47', '74'],
        answer: "22"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['61', '2', '55', '40'],
        answer: "40"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['25', '87', '84', '23'],
        answer: "84"
    },
    
     {
        question: "2 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['8', '95', '32', '22'],
        answer: "22"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['24', '58', '12', '68'],
        answer: "12"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['29', '91', '24', '96'],
        answer: "24"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['61', '71', '10', '44'],
        answer: "44"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['121', '58', '44', '3'],
        answer: "121"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['44', '18', '3', '50'],
        answer: "18"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['13', '80', '91', '22'],
        answer: "80"
    },
    
     {
        question: "2 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['30', '22', '93', '31'],
        answer: "22"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['9', '58', '1', '97'],
        answer: "9"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['77', '21', '6', '29'],
        answer: "6"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['20', '81', '69', '16'],
        answer: "20"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['59', '22', '38', '10'],
        answer: "10"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['60', '92', '88', '60'],
        answer: "60"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['2', '77', '72', '76'],
        answer: "77"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['59', '72', '8', '77'],
        answer: "8"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['43', '4', '57', '92'],
        answer: "4"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['41', '96', '44', '18'],
        answer: "18"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['95', '65', '43', '12'],
        answer: "12"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['7', '80', '91', '25'],
        answer: "80"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['57', '12', '21', '44'],
        answer: "21"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 6 = ?",
        options: ['47', '96', '65', '6'],
        answer: "6"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['25', '72', '5', '77'],
        answer: "72"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['39', '31', '75', '100'],
        answer: "100"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['40', '132', '69', '56'],
        answer: "132"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['26', '85', '8', '63'],
        answer: "63"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['10', '11', '30', '85'],
        answer: "11"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['7', '18', '20', '44'],
        answer: "44"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['27', '61', '144', '67'],
        answer: "144"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['70', '42', '15', '50'],
        answer: "50"
    },
    
     {
        question: "2 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['16', '96', '71', '6'],
        answer: "6"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['12', '89', '71', '50'],
        answer: "50"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['132', '16', '51', '34'],
        answer: "132"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['78', '72', '95', '81'],
        answer: "72"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['42', '61', '120', '22'],
        answer: "120"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['98', '48', '46', '61'],
        answer: "48"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['8', '32', '70', '32'],
        answer: "70"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['88', '75', '62', '80'],
        answer: "80"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['50', '63', '99', '33'],
        answer: "50"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['30', '27', '100', '18'],
        answer: "30"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['13', '19', '31', '35'],
        answer: "35"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['64', '94', '7', '82'],
        answer: "7"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['71', '49', '9', '64'],
        answer: "64"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['56', '63', '85', '27'],
        answer: "27"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['49', '26', '121', '63'],
        answer: "121"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['59', '79', '84', '40'],
        answer: "40"
    },
    
     {
        question: "12 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['76', '14', '24', '18'],
        answer: "24"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['1', '36', '81', '99'],
        answer: "81"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['48', '4', '11', '25'],
        answer: "48"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['49', '82', '24', '59'],
        answer: "24"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['8', '63', '22', '34'],
        answer: "63"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['83', '63', '53', '9'],
        answer: "63"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['20', '42', '7', '84'],
        answer: "20"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['9', '99', '94', '88'],
        answer: "99"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 2 = ?",
        options: ['33', '18', '46', '53'],
        answer: "18"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['72', '11', '86', '1'],
        answer: "11"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['41', '90', '35', '8'],
        answer: "35"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 11 = ?",
        options: ['56', '121', '24', '13'],
        answer: "121"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['32', '96', '28', '68'],
        answer: "32"
    },
    
     {
        question: "10 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['9', '80', '10', '67'],
        answer: "80"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['17', '22', '84', '9'],
        answer: "9"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['20', '25', '75', '17'],
        answer: "20"
    },
    
     {
        question: "2 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['20', '88', '18', '96'],
        answer: "18"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 8 = ?",
        options: ['24', '15', '83', '41'],
        answer: "24"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['56', '14', '55', '83'],
        answer: "55"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['73', '50', '55', '132'],
        answer: "132"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['9', '18', '56', '65'],
        answer: "18"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['16', '88', '88', '93'],
        answer: "16"
    },
    
     {
        question: "11 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['10', '14', '55', '75'],
        answer: "55"
    },
    
     {
        question: "5 x 10 = ?",
        options: ['94', '73', '50', '8'],
        answer: "50"
    },
    
     {
        question: "9 x 3 = ?",
        options: ['27', '47', '54', '65'],
        answer: "27"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['93', '20', '98', '93'],
        answer: "20"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['32', '52', '41', '89'],
        answer: "32"
    },
    
     {
        question: "1 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['92', '1', '98', '64'],
        answer: "1"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 4 = ?",
        options: ['91', '12', '72', '37'],
        answer: "12"
    },
    
     {
        question: "3 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['27', '32', '22', '55'],
        answer: "27"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['87', '8', '2', '78'],
        answer: "8"
    },
    
     {
        question: "4 x 9 = ?",
        options: ['36', '97', '75', '99'],
        answer: "36"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 1 = ?",
        options: ['29', '51', '79', '6'],
        answer: "6"
    },
    
     {
        question: "8 x 12 = ?",
        options: ['82', '96', '93', '60'],
        answer: "96"
    },
    
     {
        question: "6 x 5 = ?",
        options: ['71', '46', '30', '5'],
        answer: "30"
    },
    
     {
        question: "7 x 7 = ?",
        options: ['49', '91', '23', '71'],
        answer: "49"
    },
    
    
];

export default questions;